Dawid Karbowniczek

Software Developer

Software Developer with couple of years of experience in frontend development. Worked with various frameworks and technologies, now focused mostly on React. In the past, worked as a software manual tester and test engineer in big worldwide company. Always keen and opened to embrace new technologies and programming languages.

Contact

Phone

+48 609 398 947

Email

karbowniczek.daw@gmail.com

Address

linkedin.com/in/d-karbowniczek/

Education

2009 - 2013

Bachelor of Engineering

Automatic Control and Robotics

West Pomeranian University of Technology

Expertise

Web:

- HTML / CSS / RWD
- JavaScript / TypeScript

Frameworks:

- · React, Next.JS, Tailwind
- Flutter (Basic)
- Angular (Basic)

Other:

- React Hook Forms
- SWR
- Redux

Language

English - B2

Polish - Native

Projects

O Not A CV

App to help graduates find their first internship/job in UK market. Company owners can posts their job offers (web app) and graduates can looking for opportunities and apply to them (mobile app). App contains Al powered tool for recruitment automatization, where candidate profile is matched to the given role based on skills, psychometric profile, behaviours and also team dynamics.

Tech stack: React, TypeScript, Angular, Ionic, SignalR, Websockets, SWR, ApexCharts, TailwindCSS, Recoil

Start Grow Sell

Platform where entrepreneurs can assess their knowledge, against critical topic required to scale up their small company. Key features:

- Forum place where people can communicate and help each other about growing their companies
- Market here people can sell/buy advisory meetings or any kind of digital content to others
- Assessment dynamic tool to enable variety of different assessments for users

Tech stack: React, TypeScript, Next.JS, SWR, TailwindCSS, Redux

Hire My Desk

Platform which allows Hosts (Office owners) to list empty desk spaces, hiring them out to guests at a fraction of the cost. Hosts have the opportunity to reclaim revenues being lost as they pay for vacant spaces, due to their teams working less days in the office than they used to

Tech stack: React, TypeScript, Next.JS, SWR, TailwindCSS, AzureMaps

What's Yours is Mine

Shopping platform. Users can buy preowned high-end luxury fashion from a niche set of brands, but also sell used clothes to share their wardrobes.

Tech stack: React, TypeScript, Next.JS, SWR, TailwindCSS

What Would You Do

Mobile App where people can post their questions in poll format. Other people make their votes to finally visualize results with a chart.

Tech stack: Flutter, Dart

Dawid Karbowniczek

Software Developer

Software Developer with couple of years of experience in frontend development. Worked with various frameworks and technologies, now focused mostly on React. In the past, worked as a software manual tester and test engineer in big worldwide company. Always keen and opened to embrace new technologies and programming languages.

Contact

Phone

+48 609 398 947

Email

karbowniczek.daw@gmail.com

Address

linkedin.com/in/d-karbowniczek/

Education

2009 - 2013

Bachelor of Engineering

Automatic Control and Robotics

West Pomeranian University of Technology

Expertise

Web:

- HTML / CSS / RWD
- JavaScript / TypeScript

Frameworks:

- React, Next.JS, Tailwind
- Flutter (Basic)
- Angular (Basic)

Other:

- React Hook Forms
- SWR
- Redux

Language

English - B2

Polish - Native

Experience

O 01.2021 - 03.2023

FHK Technology I United Kingdom

Software Developer

- Implementing new features, components and logic based on Adobe XD designs.
- Maintaining the code, reacting on issues, implementing changes/suggestions.
- Using React + Next.JS with Tailwind CSS framework and TypeScript for most projects.
- Preparing infrastructure for API requests with OpenAPI and SWR.
- Using Flutter technology to develop mobile application.
- Working on Angular legacy project as standalone developer. Improving performance, refactoring code, adding features.
- Doing simple tasks on the backend (.NET technology) and MongoDB.
- Using SendGrid API to manage mail delivery.

05.2019 - 12.2020

DGS Poland

Software Manual Tester

- Verifying quality of software and reporting issues
- Preparing test documentation
- Assisting engineers in performing a project related duties

04.2013 - 05.2019

DGS Poland

Test Engineer

- Maintaining and improving testing stations for medical devices
- Analyzing electrical circuits of PCA Boards
- Repairing PCA Boards
- Verifying different production processes and implement change

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).